<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Arbor House Nursing Home | Traverse City Alzheimer's Care | Traverse City Dementia Care | Traverse City Nursing Home</title><link>https://arborhousealh.org/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Arbor House Nursing Home | Traverse City Alzheimer's Care | Traverse City Dementia Care | Traverse City Nursing Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://arborhousealh.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alzheimer's Care Traverse City</title><link>https://arborhousealh.org/services/alzheimers-care-traverse-city/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arborhousealh.org/services/alzheimers-care-traverse-city/</guid><description>Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease is a progressive form of dementia which is a broader term for conditions that negatively impact memory, thinking, and behavior. According to the Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s Association, Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease is the most common cause of dementia and makes up 60-80% of dementia cases. Arbor House Assisted Living specializes in caring for those who are experiencing memory loss and cognitive impairment.
What is Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s Disease? Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease is a progressive type of dementia that impacts memory, thinking, and behavior.</description></item><item><title>Assisted Living Traverse City</title><link>https://arborhousealh.org/services/assisted-living-traverse-city/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arborhousealh.org/services/assisted-living-traverse-city/</guid><description>How to Choose Assisted living When your loved one needs help with daily tasks but doesn&amp;rsquo;t need intensive medical care, assisted living may be a good option. It is a way to them live independently but in a safe and caring environment. Sometimes, assisted living can be a parge of a larger nursing care center, hospital, or senior community. Arbor house Assisted Living Home is a small assisted living facility that can accomodate up to 8 adults.</description></item><item><title>Dementia Care Traverse City</title><link>https://arborhousealh.org/services/dementia-care-traverse-city/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arborhousealh.org/services/dementia-care-traverse-city/</guid><description>Types Of dementia Although Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease is the most common cause of dementia, there are many kinds of dementia that can affect a person. If your loved one was recently diagnosed with a form of dementia it is a good idea to get an care plan in place. Arbor House Assisted Living specializes in caring for those affected by dementia.
Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease Prion proteins are found throughout the body. For reasons not understood yet, Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease is caused when these prion proteins gradually start folding into a three-dimensional shape.</description></item><item><title>Memory Care In Traverse City, Michigan</title><link>https://arborhousealh.org/services/memory-care-traverse-city/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arborhousealh.org/services/memory-care-traverse-city/</guid><description>How To Choose A Memory Care Facility Deciding which memory care facility for your loved one may feel daunting. After researching, you may find that facilities vary greatly and you may find yourself unsure of how to choose a memory care facility. It is recommended that at this point, you assess your loved one&amp;rsquo;s needs and priorities. Different facilities offer varying care services. For example, does your loved one struggle with activities related to daily living?</description></item><item><title>Nursing Home In Traverse City Michigan</title><link>https://arborhousealh.org/services/nursing-home-traverse-city/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arborhousealh.org/services/nursing-home-traverse-city/</guid><description>What Is A Nursing home Nursing homes are skilled nursing facilities that provide a wide range of health and personal care services. They are typically 24-hour staffed facilities that provide consistent meals and assistance with every day activities. They can also provide rehabilitation services, such as occupational, and speech therapy.
Some people will stay at a nursing home for a short period. However, most nursing home residents live there permanently because they have ongoing physical or mental conditions that require constant care and supervision.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://arborhousealh.org/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arborhousealh.org/about/</guid><description>Arbor House Assisted Living home (ALH) specializes in providing total care for seniors with memory loss, alzheimer’s care and dementia care. The beautiful custom built home is close to Traverse City, yet nestled alongside the Pelizzari Natural Area on a quiet wooded cul de sac on Old Mission Peninsula. The peaceful setting allows the residents to regain their sense of independence by enjoying the lush grounds and walkways which are fenced and secured.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://arborhousealh.org/contact-number/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arborhousealh.org/contact-number/</guid><description/></item><item><title>For Rent</title><link>https://arborhousealh.org/for-rent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arborhousealh.org/for-rent/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Gallery</title><link>https://arborhousealh.org/gallery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arborhousealh.org/gallery/</guid><description/></item><item><title>success</title><link>https://arborhousealh.org/success/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arborhousealh.org/success/</guid><description>Thank you for contacting Arbor House Assisted Living Home. We look forward to serving you and your family and will respond to your inquiry as soon as possible. In the meantime, feel free to check out our frequently asked questions section for more information.</description></item><item><title>Testimonials</title><link>https://arborhousealh.org/testimonial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://arborhousealh.org/testimonial/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>